Ted Koppel Collection
Ted Koppel Collection
- Nightline, 1980-2005
  - 2003
    - Nightline: Homefront: Fox 2-5 Marine Company, 01/31/2003; koppel_nl03013101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: The Loss of the Columbia, 02/03/2003; koppel_nl03020301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: The Loss of the Columbia, 02/04/2003; koppel_nl03020401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: The Evidence, 02/05/2003; koppel_nl03020501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: Fox 2-5 Marine Company: Fox 2-5 Ships Out, 02/06/2003; koppel_nl03020601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: Level Orange, 02/07/2003; koppel_nl03020701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: Flashpoint, 02/10/2003; koppel_nl03021001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: Code Orange, 02/11/2003; koppel_nl03021101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: Religion and War/Fox 2-5: Fox 2-5 Arrives in Kuwait, 02/12/2003; koppel_nl03021201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: Shoulder to Shoulder, 02/13/2003; koppel_nl03021301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: Divided Nations, 02/14/2003; koppel_nl03021401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: Fox Two-Five Marines Arrive in Kuwait and Begin Training, 02/17/2003; koppel_nl03021701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: War Stories: Fox Two-Five: Former Iraqi Now Serving with US Marines, 02/18/2003; koppel_nl03021801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: The Profiler, 02/19/2003; koppel_nl03021901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: The Price of Friendship, 02/20/2003; koppel_nl03022001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: Trapped, 02/21/2003; koppel_nl03022101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: Aftermath/Fox 2-5 Marines Train in Kuwaiti Desert, 02/24/2003; koppel_nl03022401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: Assassination, 02/25/2003; koppel_nl03022501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: The Case for War, 02/26/2003; koppel_nl03022601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: Remembering Mr. Rogers, 02/27/2003; koppel_nl03022701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: Just War, 02/28/2003; koppel_nl03022801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: Know Thy Enemy, 03/03/2003; koppel_nl03030301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: War in Iraq: Why Now?, 03/04/2003; koppel_nl03030401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: The Plan/Fox Two-Five Marines Continue Heavy Training Regimen, 03/05/2003; koppel_nl03030501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: Countdown: The President before the Nation, 03/06/2003; koppel_nl03030601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: Countdown: The Last Chance for Peace?, 03/07/2003; koppel_nl03030701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: Countdown: The Intense Lobbying For and Against War with Iraq, 03/10/2003; koppel_nl03031001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: Marsh Arabs/Preparing for War: Fox Two-Five Marines' Life in Kuwait, 03/11/2003; koppel_nl03031101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: Elizabeth Smart Found, 03/12/2003; koppel_nl03031201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: On the Edge, 03/13/2003; koppel_nl03031301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: At the Brink, 03/14/2003; koppel_nl03031401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: Moment of Truth, 03/17/2003; koppel_nl03031701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: Countdown to War, 03/18/2003; koppel_nl03031801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: War with Iraq, 03/19/2003; koppel_nl03031901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 183)
    - Nightline: War with Iraq, 03/21/2003; koppel_nl03032101
    - Nightline: War with Iraq, 03/24/2003; koppel_nl03032401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Advance on Baghdad, 03/25/2003; koppel_nl03032501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Collision Course, 03/26/2003; koppel_nl03032601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Fire Mission, 03/27/2003; koppel_nl03032701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Silent Danger, 03/28/2003; koppel_nl03032801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Destination Baghdad, 03/31/2003; koppel_nl03033101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Shooting the Gap, 04/01/2003; koppel_nl03040101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: The Tip of the Spear, 04/02/2003; koppel_nl03040201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: The Prize, 04/03/2003; koppel_nl03040301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: At the Gates, 04/04/2003; koppel_nl03040401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Downtown, 04/07/2003; koppel_nl03040701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Tightening the Grip, 04/08/2003; koppel_nl03040801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: End Game, 04/09/2003; koppel_nl03040901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: After the Fall, 04/10/2003; koppel_nl03041001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Power Vacuum, 04/11/2003; koppel_nl03041101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Between War and Peace, 04/14/2003; koppel_nl03041401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Aftershocks, 04/15/2003; koppel_nl03041501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Saddam's Weapons, 04/16/2003; koppel_nl03041601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Stolen Heritage, 04/17/2003; koppel_nl03041701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: War Stories: Untold Tales, 04/18/2003; koppel_nl03041801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Outbreak, 04/21/2003; koppel_nl03042101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Pulling the Trigger, 04/22/2003; koppel_nl03042201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Project Iraq, 04/23/2003; koppel_nl03042301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Eight of Spades, 04/24/2003; koppel_nl03042401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Backlash, 04/25/2003; koppel_nl03042501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Hometown Favorite, 04/28/2003; koppel_nl03042801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Following Orders, 04/29/2003; koppel_nl03042901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Object Lesson, 04/30/2003; koppel_nl03043001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Unfinished Business, 05/01/2003; koppel_nl03050101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Anonymous, 05/02/2003; koppel_nl03050201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Tornado Alley, 05/05/2003; koppel_nl03050501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: The Thief of Baghdad, 05/06/2003; koppel_nl03050601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Outbreak, 05/07/2003; koppel_nl03050701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: War and Politics, 05/08/2003; koppel_nl03050801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Introduction, 05/09/2003; koppel_nl03050901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Al-Qaeda Again?, 05/12/2003; koppel_nl03051201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Al-Qaeda, 05/13/2003; koppel_nl03051301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Winning the Peace, 05/14/2003; koppel_nl03051401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Troubled Times, 05/15/2003; koppel_nl03051501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Clear and Present Danger, 05/16/2003; koppel_nl03051601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Road Block, 05/19/2003; koppel_nl03051901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Code Orange, 05/20/2003; koppel_nl03052001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 184)
    - Nightline: Warren Buffett, 05/21/2003; koppel_nl03052101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: Not One of the Boys, 05/22/2003; koppel_nl03052201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: Class Action, 05/23/2003; koppel_nl03052301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: Friends Lost, 05/26/2003; koppel_nl03052601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: Messy Business, 05/27/2003; koppel_nl03052701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: Media Inc., 05/28/2003; koppel_nl03052801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: Class Reunion, 05/29/2003; koppel_nl03052901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: The Summit, 05/30/2003; koppel_nl03053001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: Hot Spot, 06/02/2003; koppel_nl03060201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: The Road to Peace, 06/03/2003; koppel_nl03060301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: Not a Good Thing, 06/04/2003; koppel_nl03060401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: The Test, 06/05/2003; koppel_nl03060501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: This Just in..., 06/06/2003; koppel_nl03060601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: The Junior Senator, 06/09/2003; koppel_nl03060901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: Unfinished Business, 06/10/2003; koppel_nl03061001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: Roadblock, 06/11/2003; koppel_nl03061101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: Hide and Seek, 06/12/2003; koppel_nl03061201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: Continent in Tragedy, 06/13/2003; koppel_nl03061301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: Cruel and Unusual Punishment, 06/16/2003; koppel_nl03061601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: Sins of the Fathers, 06/17/2003; koppel_nl03061701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: Deja Vu, 06/18/2003; koppel_nl03061801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: The Messengers, 06/19/2003; koppel_nl03061901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: The Messengers, 06/20/2003; koppel_nl03062001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: Split Decisions, 06/23/2003; koppel_nl03062301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: Man in the Middle, 06/24/2003; koppel_nl03062401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: The President's Man, 06/25/2003; koppel_nl03062501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: Coming Home, 06/26/2003; koppel_nl03062601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: Hot Spots, 06/27/2003; koppel_nl03062701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: The Great Kate, 06/30/2003; koppel_nl03063001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: Tony's Troubles, 07/01/2003; koppel_nl03070101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: Public Vows Private Lives, 07/02/2003; koppel_nl03070201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: In The National Interest, 07/03/2003; koppel_nl03070301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: The Cowboy Way, 07/04/2003; koppel_nl03070401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: Between War and Peace, 07/07/2003; koppel_nl03070701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: Hope on the Horizon, 07/08/2003; koppel_nl03070801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: On the Defensive, 07/09/2003; koppel_nl03070901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: Divine Law, 07/10/2003; koppel_nl03071001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: Informed Consent, 07/11/2003; koppel_nl03071101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: 24 Hours in Baghdad, 07/14/2003; koppel_nl03071401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: The Lost Convoy, 07/15/2003; koppel_nl03071501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: The Long Haul, 07/16/2003; koppel_nl03071601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: Food for Thought, 07/17/2003; koppel_nl03071701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 185)
    - Nightline: Kobe Charged, 07/18/2003; koppel_nl03071801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: Under Siege, 07/21/2003; koppel_nl03072101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: One Victory, 07/22/2003; koppel_nl03072201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: Total Recall, 07/23/2003; koppel_nl03072301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: Solving the Puzzle, 07/24/2003; koppel_nl03072401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: Father Raymond, 07/25/2003; koppel_nl03072501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: Bob Hope, 07/28/2003; koppel_nl03072801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: On Alert, 07/29/2003; koppel_nl03072901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: Wanted: Dead or Alive, 07/30/2003; koppel_nl03073001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: The Forgotten War, 07/31/2003; koppel_nl03073101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: Hidden Treasure, 08/01/2003; koppel_nl03080101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: Aid and Comfort, 08/04/2003; koppel_nl03080401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: Battle Fronts, 08/05/2003; koppel_nl03080501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: He Said, She Said, 08/06/2003; koppel_nl03080601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: Revenge of the Voters, 08/07/2003; koppel_nl03080701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: America in the Red: When Doing Your Best is Not Enough, 08/08/2003; koppel_nl03080801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: In the Line of Duty: Combat Casualties and US Resolve, 08/11/2003; koppel_nl03081101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: Safe Skies?, 08/12/2003; koppel_nl03081201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: Deadly Business, 08/13/2003; koppel_nl03081301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: Blackout: The Domino Effect, 08/14/2003; koppel_nl03081401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: Blackout: Power Politics, 08/15/2003; koppel_nl03081501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: Blackout: Trying to Shed Some Light, 08/18/2003; koppel_nl03081801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: Under Fire, 08/19/2003; koppel_nl03081901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: The Enemy, 08/20/2003; koppel_nl03082001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: The Innocents, 08/21/2003; koppel_nl03082101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: Moment of Crisis, 08/22/2003; koppel_nl03082201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: Little Black Box, 08/25/2003; koppel_nl03082501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: In the Line of Duty, 08/26/2003; koppel_nl03082601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: In the Extreme, 08/27/2003; koppel_nl03082701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: In Their Own Words, 08/28/2003; koppel_nl03082801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: Class Reunion, 08/29/2003; koppel_nl03082901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: Bruce Springsteen, 09/01/2003; koppel_nl03090101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: War Fronts: The Battle for Security in Iraq, 09/02/2003; koppel_nl03090201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: America in the Red, 09/03/2003; koppel_nl03090301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: The Patriot Act, 09/04/2003; koppel_nl03090401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: Prime Target, 09/05/2003; koppel_nl03090501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: Underdogs, 09/08/2003; koppel_nl03090801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: In the Line of Duty: The Soaring Costs, 09/09/2003; koppel_nl03090901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: War Fronts, 09/10/2003; koppel_nl03091001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: 9/11 2003: America Fights Back, 09/11/2003; koppel_nl03091101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: War Stories: Reporting from the Front Lines, 09/12/2003; koppel_nl03091201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: Recall, 09/15/2003; koppel_nl03091501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 186)
    - Nightline: A Conversation with Condoleezza Rice, 09/16/2003; koppel_nl03091601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: War Stories: Soldiers, Victims and Saviors, 09/17/2003; koppel_nl03091701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: Isabel, 09/18/2003; koppel_nl03091801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: The Road to Kandahar, 09/19/2003; koppel_nl03091901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: Survival of the Fittest, 09/22/2003; koppel_nl03092201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: Security Breech, 09/23/2003; koppel_nl03092301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: The Occupation, 09/24/2003; koppel_nl03092401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: The General, 09/25/2003; koppel_nl03092501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: Galileo, 09/26/2003; koppel_nl03092601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: Game Plan, 09/29/2003; koppel_nl03092901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: The Investigation, 09/30/2003; koppel_nl03093001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: Bottom Line, 10/01/2003; koppel_nl03100101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: Crossing the Line?, 10/02/2003; koppel_nl03100201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: Spies, 10/03/2003; koppel_nl03100301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: The Mud Pit, 10/06/2003; koppel_nl03100601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: California Recall [EARLY EDITION], 10/07/2003; koppel_nl03100701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: California Recall [LATE EDITION], 10/07/2003; koppel_nl03100702; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: Report Card, 10/08/2003; koppel_nl03100801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: The Bombers, 10/09/2003; koppel_nl03100901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: Lovable Losers, 10/10/2003; koppel_nl03101001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: Great Escape, 10/13/2003; koppel_nl03101301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: Crowded Space, 10/14/2003; koppel_nl03101401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: Adjusting the Filter, 10/15/2003; koppel_nl03101501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: On the Edge, 10/16/2003; koppel_nl03101601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: R and R, 10/17/2003; koppel_nl03101701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: Critical Condition: In a Place Called Englewood, 10/20/2003; koppel_nl03102001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: Critical Condition: The Power of Death and Life, 10/21/2003; koppel_nl03102101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: Critical Condition: The Mind of a Jury, 10/22/2003; koppel_nl03102201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: Critical Condition: US Health Care v. The World, 10/23/2003; koppel_nl03102301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: Critical Condition: The ER in Crisis, 10/24/2003; koppel_nl03102401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: Firestorm: In the Heat of the Battle, 10/27/2003; koppel_nl03102701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: Firestorm: The Growing Devastation in Southern California, 10/28/2003; koppel_nl03102801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: Firestorm: On the Front Lines, 10/29/2003; koppel_nl03102901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: Firestorm: Lessons from the Ashes, 10/30/2003; koppel_nl03103001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: On Edge, 10/31/2003; koppel_nl03103101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: Death Toll, 11/03/2003; koppel_nl03110301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: Iraq: Where Things Stands, 11/04/2003; koppel_nl03110401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: The Fix, 11/05/2003; koppel_nl03110501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: Nasty Business, 11/06/2003; koppel_nl03110601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: Casualties of War, 11/07/2003; koppel_nl03110701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: Super Human, 11/10/2003; koppel_nl03111001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: Shattered Lives, 11/11/2003; koppel_nl03111101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: Rules of Engagement, 11/12/2003; koppel_nl03111201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 187)
    - Nightline: The Quiet American, 11/13/2003; koppel_nl03111301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: Afghan Stories, 11/14/2003; koppel_nl03111401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: Hearts and Minds, 11/17/2003; koppel_nl03111701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: Culture Wars, 11/18/2003; koppel_nl03111801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: The Case Against Michael Jackson, 11/19/2003; koppel_nl03111901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: A World of Hurt, 11/20/2003; koppel_nl03112001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: America in Black and White: A Question of Identity, 11/21/2003; koppel_nl03112101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: Battlefronts in Iraq, 11/24/2003; koppel_nl03112401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: The List, 11/25/2003; koppel_nl03112501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: Dear America, 11/26/2003; koppel_nl03112601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: Thanksgiving Stories, 11/27/2003; koppel_nl03112701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: On the Move, 11/28/2003; koppel_nl03112801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: Firefight, 12/01/2003; koppel_nl03120101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: Standing Up, 12/02/2003; koppel_nl03120201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: America in Black and White: Reparations for Slavery, 12/03/2003; koppel_nl03120301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: Marine Company Fox 2-5: Back to the Future, 12/04/2003; koppel_nl03120401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: Marine Company Fox 2-5: A Jarring Portrait of War, 12/05/2003; koppel_nl03120501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: War Stories: Living and Dying in Iraq, 12/08/2003; koppel_nl03120801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: Vote 2004: The New Hampshire Democratic Debates, 12/09/2003; koppel_nl03120901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: A Good Death, 12/10/2003; koppel_nl03121001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: Terror Network, 12/11/2003; koppel_nl03121101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: Instruments of Peace, 12/12/2003; koppel_nl03121201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: The Prisoner: After the Capture, 12/15/2003; koppel_nl03121501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: The Prisoner: Justice Under Pressure, 12/16/2003; koppel_nl03121601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: Moving Targets, 12/17/2003; koppel_nl03121701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: 9/11/2011, 12/18/2003; koppel_nl03121801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: Reality Check, 12/19/2003; koppel_nl03121901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: Code Orange, 12/22/2003; koppel_nl03122201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: Mad Cow, 12/23/2003; koppel_nl03122301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: Tis the Season, 12/24/2003; koppel_nl03122401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: White Christmas, 12/25/2003; koppel_nl03122501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: The Ultimate Gift, 12/26/2003; koppel_nl03122601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: Epicenter, 12/29/2003; koppel_nl03122901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: War Stories: Behind the Scenes in Iraq, 12/30/2003; koppel_nl03123001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
  - 2004
    - Nightline: Encore, 01/01/2004; koppel_nl04010101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: Stryker Brigade, 01/02/2004; koppel_nl04010201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)
    - Nightline: Code Orange, 01/05/2004; koppel_nl04010501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 188)